let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the tag of image in html?",
        answer: "C. < img > tag",
        options: [
            "A. < images> tag ",
            "B. < imagestag >",
            "C. < img > tag",  
            "D. < /img > tag",  
        ]
    },
    {
    numb: 2,
        question: "What is the tag of paragraphs in html?.",
        answer: "D. < p > tag",
        options: [
            "A. < parag > tag",
            "B. < paragraph > tag", 
            "C. < /parag > tag",
            "D. < p > tag"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is the html links tag?",
        answer: "A. < a >",
        options: [
            "A. < a >", 
            "B. < b >", 
            "C. < c >", 
            "D. < d >" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What does <h1> tags means in html? ",
        answer: "B. to indicate the primary topic in web page",
        options: [
            "A. to appear the phrase: this is a heading",
            "B. to indicate the primary topic in web page",
            "C. to appear the closing tag",
            "D. to appear the text title"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the purpose of html headings?",
        answer: "D. to index the structure and content of the web page",
        options: [
            "A. to search engines", 
            "B. to show the document structure", 
            "C. to index the structure", 
            "D. to index the structure and content of the web page",

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Where does the HTML paragraph appear? ",
        answer: "C. between the opening < p > tag and the closing < /p > tag",
        options: [
            "A. between the opening < /p > tag", 
            "B. between closing < p > tag", 
            "C. between the opening < p > tag and the closing < /p > tag", 
            "D. on a new line" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Where are html documents made? ",
        answer: "C. by html elements",
        options: [
            "A. on a server computer", 
            "B. on a web-browser", 
            "C. by html elements", 
            "D. by structured documents" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What does html documents can be nested mean? ",
        answer: "A. elements can contain other elements",
        options: [
            "A. elements can contain other elements",
            "B. to process of storing data",
            "C. elements have a function inside of another function",
            "D. to nested with unordered elements"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Where should HTML documents start? ",
        answer: "B. to < !Doctype html >",
        options: [
            "A. to < html > and ends with < /html >",
            "B. to < !Doctype html >",
            "C. to < h1 > My first heading",
            "D. to < p > My first paragraph"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What is the < p > tag used for? ",
        answer: "B. to defines a paragraph",
        options: [
            "A. to add a single blank line before and after each <p> element", 
            "B. to defines a paragraph", 
            "C. to represents a visual media", 
            "D. to start the documents"            

        ]
    },
]